(line ringing)
(Sheldon:)Hello.
SHELDON:
Hello.
(Sheldon:)Listen, I've been
thinking a lot
(Sheldon:)about relationships
(Sheldon:)and how difficult they can be,
and I think...
(Sheldon:)I've been thinking
about them, too, Sheldon.
(Amy:)Being your girlfriend
is so challenging.
(Amy:)Emotionally,
(Amy:)physically.
(Amy:)I've been incredibly patient
for years.
(Sheldon:)Strongly disagree.
(Sheldon:)Go on.
(Leonard:)Okay, well...
(Amy:)this isn't easy to say,
because I love you,
(Sheldon:)but...
(Amy:)I need some time
to take a step back
(Amy:)and reevaluate our situation.
(Amy:)Oh.
(Amy:)I hope you understand.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Amy:)Bye, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Well, Gollum...
(Sheldon:)...you're an expert on rings.
(Sheldon:)What do I do with this one?